l can't help it,
l feel like a teen heartthrob.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I used to cut my brother's hair.
l could do it.
(Sheldon:)Penny, I know you mean well,
offering the skills of the hill folk...
...but here in town,
we don't churn our own butter...
...we don't make dresses
out of gunny sacks...
...and we sure as shooting
don't get our hair cut by bottle-blond...
(Leonard:)Sheldon, be nice.
I'm sorry, it's the bad-boy attitude
that comes with this hair.
(Raj:)You could go to my guy.
He's at Juan-Juan in Beverly Hills.
(Raj:)They bring you a cup of tea,
massage your scalp.
It's $200 but sometimes
you look in the next chair...
(Raj:)...and you see a superstar
like Tony Danza.
(Howard:)Quick question here, have we actually
changed the conversation...
...from "I'm going to astronaut training"
to "Sheldon can't get a haircut"?
Now who's dying ofjealousy?
"Oh," it's you.